For more videos, please subscribe to our channel and click on the bell icon for latest updates.
Mother's Talk
In a village, a Brahmin used to live with his mother.
One day, a Brahmin had to go to another village.
He used to be a Brahmin.
Then his mother used to say,
Why do you go alone?
You can take anyone with you.
Then the Brahmin used to say,
True, I have to go in the way of asking.
But in that question, there are no diseases.
He says there are no thieves.
But it would be nice if anyone comes with you.
Mother, don't be afraid.
I will go alone and come back home tomorrow evening.
But the mother doesn't like to go alone.
With this, she goes to the garden near the house.
She takes a stone from the garden.
I don't agree to go alone.
She says, Take this stone and keep it with you.
She takes the stone to make her mother happy.
She puts it in her bag.
After that, she takes the stone and starts her journey.
That is the first time.
That Brahmin can't touch the end.
Then he sees a big stone.
He thinks that he will take the stone along with him.
The Brahmin eats his food and takes the stone.
He takes the stone along with him.
The Brahmin gets up in the middle of the night.
In the same stone, there is a snake.
The snake that comes out of the stone looks at the snake near the Brahmin.
The snake immediately comes near the snake.
It eats the food in the snake.
The snake looks at it and gets angry.
It immediately hunts the snake.
It kills the snake.
After killing the snake, the Brahmin gets up.
He immediately looks at the snake.
There, he notices that the snake is dead near the snake.
He thinks that the snake saved his life from the snake.
He turns the snake into a snake.
He thinks that he should listen to the mother's words carefully.
He should listen to the elders' words carefully.
Subscribe to our channel.
Also, don't forget to share this video to your friends.
Okay, bye. Let's meet again.