There was a great teacher in a village.
He was a farmer.
One day, he was invited to a press conference.
He was told that he would reach more than 10,000 people.
He was invited to a press conference.
When he came to the press conference,
there was no one there.
Only this teacher was there.
The teacher who had made a lot of conversation with him,
had a big change.
He thought about what to do.
He asked the farmer.
After that,
He said,
When he went to the field,
he went out of the field.
Even if there was only one field,
I would come out with the field that I needed.
He said so.
This teacher was like a snake in his eye.
He started his presentation by putting a sabaash.
He presented a great presentation
by putting a sabaash.
After that,
He asked the farmer,
How was my conversation?
After that,
I was a farmer.
I didn't know anything.
If there was only one farmer in the field,
I would come out with the field that I needed.
Even if there was only one farmer in the field,
I wouldn't come out with the field that I needed.
He said so.
The face of the teacher was lost.
We have to say whatever they need,
whatever they understand.
If we are in a place where we don't need
to know anything,
they will say,
We are the eggs.