In a very big tree in the field, it was very green.
It was also covered with leaves.
One day, a child was going to that field.
It was also very hot.
He saw that there was a very big tree in front of it.
And there were leaves on that tree.
After seeing the leaves, water came into his mouth.
He thought that he should rest a little after his stomach.
He slept for a while in the shade of the tree.
After a while, he woke up and left.
The next day, he was standing there and laughing.
He saw that tree.
He said that there is not a single tree in the tree.
He asked, where did all the leaves go?
The tree said that all the leaves were eaten.
But if you give him water, then I will give you a lot of leaves.
That tree was given water every day.
After a few days, the tree was given fruit.
After seeing the fruit, he was very happy.
We get this story so easily.
That we should give water to the tree plants.
In return, we give good weather, fruit and vegetables to the tree.